<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TrivialMe</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TrivialMe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What &amp; Why of this website</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Since quite some time I have been maintaining a notebook with ideas that cross my mind.
These are ideas that are directly influenced by the miniscule amount of knowledge that I have and hence are, by all means, trivial in nature. Hence my only intention with this website is to put forward a (hopefully) unique perspective on topics that I am interested in. The topics can range from science to philosophy and religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Division by zero</title>
      <link>/division_by_zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/division_by_zero/</guid>
      <description>When you search for the phrase &amp;ldquo;division by zero&amp;rdquo; on Google, you get many unique takes on this problem. The general theme of all explanations is &amp;ldquo;You can&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo;. Some explanations even introduce new different form of number lines in an attempt to get to an answer for division by zero, which I think is pretty cool.
You might even wonder &amp;ndash; is there even a possibility of adding more to to this than what already exists?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning by guided discovery</title>
      <link>/learning_by_guided_discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learning_by_guided_discovery/</guid>
      <description> Set the context and establish what is already known and believed to be true. Ask a question that can be derived from already eastablished context. Try and answer the question. Add answer to already established context. Repeat until satisfied.
context = setup what is already known learn() { while (not satisfied) { // dsdds questions = ask_questions_from(context); foreach question of questions { answer = try_answer(question); append(context, answer); } } }   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>