<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tiny Blobs</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tiny Blobs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About this website...</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Like a multitude of people, I rejoice wondering about the ultimate meaning and purpose of life (it&amp;rsquo;s probably not 42) and thinking about connections between things that don&amp;rsquo;t seem connected on the surface. Unlike many people, I never wrote anything down. Then one day I decided to give it a try and started recording my thoughts in a diary. After not very long, it became one of my most personal possessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Division by zero</title>
      <link>/division_by_zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/division_by_zero/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sir, if no banana was distributed to no student, then will each student get one banana?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; a question famously attributed to Ramanujan. Although on the surface it sounds meaningless, it cuts right to heart of mathematics and it&amp;rsquo;s interpretation. Should zero not be treated like other numbers because it does not make sense to have zero of anything in real life? Or should it be the other way round? &amp;ndash; in which case Ramanujan&amp;rsquo;s question should have an answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning by guided discovery</title>
      <link>/learning_by_guided_discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learning_by_guided_discovery/</guid>
      <description>Some more context to offset the code block which does not look very good in the index.
 Set the context and establish what is already known and believed to be true. Ask a question that can be derived from already eastablished context. Try and answer the question. Add answer to already established context. Repeat until satisfied.   context = setup what is already known learn() { while (not satisfied) { // dsdds questions = ask_questions_from(context); foreach question of questions { answer = try_answer(question); append(context, answer); } } }  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>